Guide to the Howard Scott Labor Ephemera Collection, 1894-2004 AIS.1999.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Howard Scott Labor Ephemera Collection
1894-2004
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Scott, Howard
AIS.1999.09
5 Linear Feet (3 boxes and 2 oversize photographs)
This collection includes photographs, ephemera, buttons and badges purchased by Howard Scott to create a comprehensive body of artifacts documenting working class culture in western Pennsylvania during the twentieth century.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Howard Scott in June 1999 and February 2006.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection includes photographs, ephemera, buttons and badges which represent working class culture in western Pennsylvania during the twentieth century. Unions represented in this collection include: United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America; United Auto Workers; Service Employees International Union; United Mine Workers of America; Brotherhood of Teamsters; and various western Pennsylvania union locals. The American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations are also represented, both before and after their 1955 merger. Throughout the finding aid, descriptions in quotations signify textual incriptions on the actual item.
Custodial History
These materials were purchased by Howard Scott through private individuals at flea markets, antique shows, and various sales before being acquired by the University of Pittsburgh.
History
This collection includes items documenting working class culture in western Pennsylvania collected by Howard Scott. Scott purchased these pins, buttons, badges, ribbons, and ephemera at flea markets, antique shows, and various sales before selling them to the University of Pittsburgh, making them available for research use.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Arrangement
The collection has been arranged into the following series:
Series I. Ephemera
Series II. Photographs
Series III. Badges and Pins
Previous Citation
Howard Scott Labor Ephemera Collection, 1894-2004, AIS.1999.09, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Labor; Buttons (Information artifacts); Badges; Photographs; Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; AFL-CIO; Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.); American Federation of Labor; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (A.F. of L.); Service Employees International Union; United Mine Workers of America
- Ephemera, I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series includes postcards depicting labor unions, leaders, and work places throughout the Pittsburgh area. Also included are pamphlets and fliers regarding meetings and elections. Union membership cards and dues books are present, as well as letters from a soldier who was deployed to the 1894 coal miners' strike in Wallston, Pennsylvania.
  - "Martyrs of the 8-Hours Day - Pittsburgh District" by John F. Gloeckner, 1917; 1. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Socialist Candidates For President, Norman Thomas, and Vice-President, James H. Maurer", Pamphlet, 1928; 2.
  - Specimen Ballot, McKean County, PA, 1923; 3.
  - "South Yards - P.&L.E.R.R., McKees Rocks, Pa." Postcard, 1912; 4.
  - Flyer for Meeting regarding P.&.L.E.R.R. vs. American Federation of Labor, et al., August 4, 1922; 5.
  - State Gazette, Trenton, NJ, with Article regarding Iron Work in Pittsburgh, February 23, 1850; 6.
  - Letters from a Soldier in Company D, 16th Regiment in Wallston, Jefferson County, PA, during a Coal Miners Strike, June 25-26, 1894; 7-8.
  - John O'Malley Membership Card and Monthly Stamp Book, Bartenders International Union Local 188, 1948-1951; 9.
  - Alton Harris Membership Book and Quarterly Working Card, International Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers Union Local 11, 1952; 10.
  - "Bread Line - McKees Rocks Strike" Postcard, 11.
  - "I.A.T.S.E. Local No. 8, Phila., PA. Fourth Annual Christmas Party" Postcard, December 24, 1941; 12.
  - Lane Kirkland: Notable People Card, 13.
  - Official Souvenir Watch Fab, Pittsburgh Temple Dedication, 1910; 1. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Union Labor Temple, Webster Avenue and Epiphany Street, Pittsburgh, Pa." Postcard, 2.
- Photographs, II.
  This series includes photographs depicting activites of steel and mine workers' unions. Also included are several unlabeled photographs of workers and immigrants.
  - Photograph Prints, 1.
    This subseries contains photographs documenting the beginnings of the mine and steel workers unions. Also included are several unlabeled photos depicting immigrants at Ellis Island, African American workers, convention delegates and labor uprisings.
    - Eastern Pennsylvania UMWA Picket against Gangloff Bros. and P.P.&L., 1. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Buhl Day Parade Car, Retail Clerks Union Local 1331, 2.
    - Immigrants at Ellis Island, 3-6.
    - Riot, 7.
    - Amalgamated Association of Iron, Steel and Tin Workers, Beaver Valley Lodge No. 200 March, 1930s; 8.
    - Duquesne Smelting Co., Workers Pouring, 1946; 9.
    - African American Delegates, 1942; 10.
    - Delegates, CIO Annual Convention, 1951; 11.
    - Picketers Attacking Mail Truck, Jones & Laughlin Plant in Aliquippa, PA, May 13, 1937; 1. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Prisoners from Coal Mine Strike in Wildwood, PA, June 22, 1931; 2.
    - Worker Gathering, 3.
    - Philip Murray Launching the Steelworkers Organizing Committee, 1936; 4.
    - Dairymen Delivering Milk Under Police Escort During the Pittsburgh Milk Strike, June 14, 1950; 5.
    - William Z. Foster and Mother Jones in a Group of Steel Organizers during the Steel Strike, 1919; 6.
  - Oversize Photographs, 2.
    This subseries is comprised of two oversize photographs. The first depicts Philip Murray, president of the United Steelworkers of America, addressing the eleventh annual District 7 conference in 1951. The other photograph shows the members of the Steelworkers Organizing Committee in 1944.
    - Philip P. Murray-11th Annual United Steelworkers of America District 7 Conference, 1951; 1. (Map-case 3, Drawer 15)
    - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1944; 2. (Map-case 3, Drawer 15)
- Badges and Pins, III.
  This series includes buttons, pins and badges that would have been worn by the workers in western Pennsylvania. National and local union buttons and badges from conventions, labor strikes, and celebrations, such as Labor Day, are represented, as well as those reflecting the payment of union dues. Also included are campaign buttons for union, local and presidential elections.
  - "Job Security. Union Conditions. Vote UE.", 1. (Map-case 3, Tray 1)
  - "Unity For Defense: United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers", 2.
  - "11th International Convention UE-CIO Milwaukee, Wisc.", 1948; 3.
  - "UE Member: United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers", 4.
  - "UE: United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America", 5-6.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A. Local 301: Dues Paid", 1938; 7.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A. Local 301: Sept.", 8.
  - "Wear Union Stamped Shoes: Boot & Shoe Workers' Union", 9.
  - "U.E.R.M.W. of A. Local 702 Steward", 10.
  - "UE: Higher Pay. Shorter Hours. Stop Layoffs.", 11.
  - "Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Company: 5 Years Service", 12.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A. Local 301: March", 13.
  - "One Nation. One Flag. One Union. Vote UE for Collective Bargaining", 14.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A. Local 301", 15.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A. Local 301", 1938; 16.
  - "United Brotherhood of Electrical Workers: I Support Prussack Strikers Rep. Dist. 12 U.E.&R.W.A. CIO", 17.
  - "10% War Bond Buyer Koppers Co. A.H.P.R. Div.", 18.
  - "United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America: UE Local 1180 Sioux Falls", 1984; 19.
  - "Save Our Jobs Vote IUE-CIO", 20.
  - "United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America: Member Local 107", 21.
  - "United Farm Equipment Workers of America", May 1942; 22.
  - Employee Photo Identification Button, United States Steel Corp. Christy Park Works, 23.
  - Employee Photo Identification Button, Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Company, 24.
  - Employee Photo Identification Button, Union Switch & Signal, Swissvale, PA, 25.
  - "Win with IUE CIO", 26.
  - "U.E.&R.W. of A. St. Louis Dist.", May 1937; 1. (Map-case 3, Tray 2)
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A. Dist. 8", May 1938; 2.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A. Dist. 8", February 1940; 3.
  - "United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America: UE Local 107", 4.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: I Helped the Century Strikers To Win Better Union Wages and Conditions", 5.
  - "Let's Make It 100% U.A.W.-C.I.O.", 6.
  - "UE Organizing Committee", 7.
  - "U.E.&R.W. of A. St. Louis Dist.", November 1937; 8.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", September 1941; 9.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", July 1941; 10.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", February 1938; 11.
  - "Oil Workers International Union CIO", July-September 1942; 12.
  - "United Packinghouse Workers of America: U.P.W.A. C.I.O.", January-March 1951; 13.
  - "United Packinghouse Workers of America Affiliated CIO", January-March 1946; 14.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", December 1938; 15.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", November 1940; 16.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", October 1939; 17.
  - "U.R.W. of A.", September 1937; 18.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", April 1939; 19.
  - "U.E.&R.W. of A.: St. Louis Dist.", July 1937; 20.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", March 1940; 21.
  - "Vollrath Workers Union: UE Local 167", 22.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", April 1938; 23.
  - "Oil Workers International Union", July-September 1941; 24.
  - "Local #7, U.R.W. of A.", July 1938; 25.
  - "U.R.W. of A. C.I.O", 1943; 26.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", September 1941; 27.
  - "UE-CIO: We Need A Wage Increase Now!", 28.
  - "United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America: Chief Steward C.I.O.", 29.
  - "Job Security. Union Conditions. Vote UE", 30.
  - "Save Our Jobs Vote IUE-CIO", 31.
  - "Local 2016 U.R.R.W.A. C.I.O.", 32.
  - "My Shop Is I.U.M.S.W.A. 100%: C.I.O. All For One-One For All", 33.
  - "U.A.W.-C.I.O.", January-February 1954; 34.
  - "I.W. of A. C.I.O. Local No.34 - Dist. 3: Feb", 35.
  - "U.E.R.&M.W. of A.: Dist. 8", January 1938; 36.
  - "FTA CIO", 37.
  - "United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America: U.E. Member", 38.
  - "United Farm Equipment Workers of America, Affiliated with CIO", March 1943; 39.
  - "United Farm Equipment & Metal Workers C.I.O.", March 1946; 40.
  - "UE Local 1150", October-December 1955; 41.
  - "United Packinghouse Workers of America: U.P.W.A. C.I.O.", October-December 1951; 42.
  - "Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers: United Mine Workers of America CIO District 50", 43.
  - "United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America: UE", 44.
  - "American Federation of Labor: Pittsburgh" Badge, 1905; 1. (Box 2, Tray 1)
  - "UMWA 3rd Biennial Convention, Indianapolis" Badge, 1918; 2.
  - "Workingmen of Donora, PA Fourth Annual Outing, Kennywood Park" Badge, August 15, 1914; 3.
  - "Delegate First Constitutional Convention CIO" Badge, November 1938; 4.
  - "Delegate: Steel Workers Organizing Committee Wage and Policy Convention" Badge, December 14, 1937; 5.
  - "15th Annual Convention District No.2 UMWA: Altoona, PA." Badge, March 15, 1904; 6.
  - "Labor Day Celebration: A.F.G.W.U., S.S. Pittsburg, Pennsylvania", 7.
  - "C.I.O. Pennsylvania Industrial Union Council: 12th Annual Convention, Harrisburg" Delegate Badge, May 17, 1949; 8.
  - "50th Flood Anniversary Remembrance Day St. Michael, PA.: Hall-Moriarity Post No. 551 American Legion" Badge, May 31, 1939; 9.
  - Pittsburgh Unity Council Button, 10.
  - Ceramic Labor Day Medallion, Pittsburgh, PA, 1904; 11.
  - "U.M.W. of A. 2nd Biennial Convention, 8 Hours" Badge, 1916; 12.
  - "Delegate 19th Annual Convention Pennsylvania C.I.O. Council, Pittsburgh, PA" Badge, March 13-16, 1956; 13.
  - "Delegate 40th Consecutive and 15th Biennial Convention U.M.W. of A., Pittsburgh, PA" Badge, February 1946; 14.
  - "B. of L.E. 406 and B. of L.F.&E. 381 Picnic, Luna Park", July 29, 1914; 15.
  - "United Labor League of Western Pennsylvania, Labor Day 100 Yard Dash" Badge, 1924; 1. (Box 2, Tray 2)
  - "John Dresmich, Official: National First Aid & Mine Rescue Contest" Department of the Interior, Bureau of Mines, Fort Wayne, IN, 1953; 2.
  - "M. John Dorsey, Executive and Finance Committee: Pittsburgh Central Labor Union" Badge, 1948; 3.
  - "Mrs. Marie Mazie, 17th Annual Convention, Associated Master Barbers & Beauticians of Pennsylvania" Guest Badge, October 3-5, 1943; 4.
  - "Pittsburger Turnbezirks, Bezirks Turnfest: Altoona" Badge, June 25-27, 1914; 5.
  - "U.M.W. of A. Local Union 3715 Indianola, PA", 6.
  - "Brotherhood of Teamsters Committee, Pittsburgh" Badge, July 4, 1908; 7.
  - "International Association of Machinists Reunion, Alliquippa Park", August 22, 1903; 8.
  - "U.B. of C.&J. of A. Pittsburgh Delegation" Badge, 9.
  - "Delegate 10th International Convention United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America C.I.O., New York City" Badge, September 24-29, 1944; 10-14.
  - "Gen'l Vice-Pres. 8th National Convention U.E.R.&M.W. of A., Indianapolis" Badge, September 1942; 15.
  - "Delegate 42nd Consecutive and 16th Constitutional Convention Dist. No. 5 U.M.W. of A." Badge, June 13, 1950; 16.
  - "Official Souvenir: Labor's National Holiday, Pittsburgh, Penn. 6th Annual Labor Day Demonstration" Badge, September 5th, 1904; 17.
  - "Jr.O.U.A.M.: Mound City Council 6" Junior Order of United American Mechanics Badge, 18.
  - "Delegate United Mine Workers of America, Atlantic City, NJ" Badge, 1946; 1. (Box 2, Tray 3)
  - "C.I.O. Pennsylvania Industrial Union Council: 10th Annual Convention, Harrisburg" Delegate Badge, April 22, 1947; 2.
  - "C.I.O. Pennsylvania Industrial Union Council: 9th Annual Convention, Pittsburgh" Delegate Badge, April 30, 1946; 3.
  - Front: "New Kensington Lodge No.115 A.A. of I.S. and T.W. of N.A. New Kensington, Penna.", Back: "In Memoriam" Badge, 4.
  - "Member: Holbrook Lodge, No.378 B. of L.F.&E. McKees Rocks, PA." Badge, 5.
  - "Mckeesport Liederkranz" Badge, 6.
  - "John Sperrings, Past President Victory Lodges No.50 Carnegie, PA." Badge, 7.
  - "General Committee Pittsburgh, PA, Labor Day Celebration" Badge, September 2, 1901; 8.
  - "Delegate 38th Consecutive and 11th Biennial Convention, U.M.W. of America District No.5 Pittsburgh" Badge, October 1937; 9.
  - "Delegate 13th Annual Convention Penna CIO Council, Pittsburgh" Badge, March 28-30, 1950; 10.
  - "Washington Lodge No.1 Member I.A. of T.W., Washington, PA" Badge, 11.
  - "Zelatorka" Polish Badge with Biblical Verse, 12.
  - "Official Badge of the Iron City Central Trades Council, Labor Day Pittsburgh, Pa.", 1913; 13.
  - Front: "Logen Engelbrekt No. 148 Vasa Orden, Warren, PA.", Back "In Memoriam, V.O." Swedish Badge, 14.
  - "Member U.M.W. of A. Local 5750 Westmoreland City, Penna." Badge, 15.
  - "Member UMW of America Local 6559 Central Mine of Tarrs, PA" Badge, 16.
  - "Local Union No.22 Member Brewery Workers Union of America, Pittsburgh and Vicinity" Badge, 17.
  - "Jr.O.U.A.M.: Schenley Park Council 5" Junior Order of United American Mechanics Badge, 18.
  - "Local Union No.144 Bottlers I.U. of U.B.W. of A." Badge, 19.; Item is currently on loan to the Constitution Center, due to arrive back to the ASC on 8/31/2011.
  - "Local Union No. 202, Carpenter's Union, U.B. of C.&J. of A." Badge, 20.; Item is currently on loan to the Constitution Center, due to arrive back to the ASC on 8/31/2011.
  - "SEIU Yes", 1. (Box 3, Tray 1)
  - "Service Employees Local 150", 2-4.
  - "AFL-CIO SEIU CLC", 5.
  - "I'm Sweet on the Union! COGS-SEIU Local 150 AFL-CIO", 6.
  - "$1.00: It's Time/Ya Es Hora" UE Button, 7.
  - "Take the Cap Off: Save Social Security" UE Button, 8.
  - "Be Free Vote UE", 9.
  - "United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America Chief Steward", 10.
  - "United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America Steward", 11.
  - "United Electrical & Radio Workers of America C.I.O. Local 601, Feb.", 12.
  - UE Pen Clips, 13-16.
  - "March on Harrisburg: Keep TMI Shut Down. March 28", 17.
  - "They Lie" Three Mile Island Button Featuring Jules Feiffer Cartoon, 18.
  - "McGovern/Shriver", 19.
  - "Take the Chisholm Trail to 1600 Pennsylvania Ave", 20.
  - "Catalyst For Change: Shirley Chisholm for President", 21.
  - "My Token, I've Registered", 22.
  - "I Gave in '54, For Jobs in '55: Elect Pro-Labor Congress", 1955; 23.
  - "Able/Kluz: Burke-Johns" Campaign Button, 24.
  - "Labor Day, Punxsutawney, PA", 1919; 25.
  - "Greater Pittsburg's Greatest Labor Day", September 1, 1902; 26.
  - "United Labor Carnival May 30 to June 13, Pittsburgh PA", 27.
  - "A.F. of L.-C.O.P.E. PGH C.L.U. Adlai and Estes", 28.
  - "AF of L: United Textile Workers of America", 29.
  - "A.F. of L. C.F.P.A. of PGH, PA", 30.
  - "Cleaning & Dye House Workers Aff. with A.F. of L.", 1939; 31.
  - "Union 15938 A.F. of L. of Waynesboro, PA", November 1919; 32.
  - "U.G.W. of A. A.F. of L.", 33.
  - "A.F. of L.: United Cement, Lime & Gypsum Workers Int'l Union", 34.
  - "A.F. of L. for PGH. C.L.U. Leader", 35.
  - "A.F. of L. Committee, Political Action Allegheny County: Earle-Jones/Mundy-Logue", 36.
  - "A.M.C.&B.W. of N.A. Canning & Pickle Workers 325", December 1939; 37.
  - "A.M.C.&B.W. of N.A. Canning & Pickle Workers 325", January 1940; 38.
  - "Vote United Faculty: University of Pittsburgh", 39.
  - "AF of T", 40.
  - "Hospital Division 99 AFL-CIO", 41.
  - "UFCW Local 23 AFL-CIO-CLC", 42.
  - "Upholsterers Int. Union of N.A., A.F. of L.", 43.
  - "National Federation of Post Office Clerks", 44.
  - "American Federation of Grain Millers", 45.
  - "Bldg. Service Employees Int'l Union", 46.
  - "Insurance Agents International Union", 47.
  - Pittsburgh Fraternal Order of Police Pin, 48.
  - "Laundry Workers Intl. Union", 49.
  - "I.B.&C.W.U. of A." Bakery & Confectionery Workers Union Pin, 50.
  - "State, County and Municipal Workers of America, CIO", May 1942; 51.
  - "S.W.O.C., C.I.O.: America's First Line of Defense", 52.
  - "CIO Canvasser: Political Action Committee", 53.
  - "I Am Your Neighbor: CIO Community Political Action Committee", 54.
  - "CIO Political Action Committee: Authorized Precinct Captain", 55.
  - "I.A. of M." International Association of Machinists Pin, 56.
  - "IA of M Committee Member", 57.
  - "I.B.E.W., A.F. of L.", 58.
  - "CWA-CIO: Communication Workers of America", 59.
  - "International Brotherhood of Operative Potters", 60.
  - "United Paperworkers International Union, AFL-CIO-CLC", 61.
  - "United Paper, Novelty & Toy Workers Int. Union", 62.
  - "National Association of Stationary Engineers", 63.
  - "IUE: International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried & Machine Workers, AFL-CIO", 64.
  - "Int. Bro. of Blacksmiths: Drop Foggers & Helpers Dist. Council 5, 3rd Quarter", 1943; 65.
  - "IBPAT" International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades Pin, 66.
  - "Paint Makers 1310, A.F. of L., Second Quarter", 1942; 67.
  - "Pittsburgh Building Trades Council", October-December 1914; 68.
  - "Pittsburgh Building & Cons't Trades Council, Steam Fitters", October-December 1960; 69.
  - "Pittsburgh Building & Cons't Trades Council, Plumbers", January-March 1961; 70.
  - "Erie Building Trades Council", January-March 1918; 71.
  - "United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America", 72.
  - "Excavating, Coal Dump Truck Drivers & Helpers 341", November 1953; 73.
  - "Const. Gen'l. Labor & Material Handlers 1058", April-June 1958; 74.
  - "I.M.&F.W.U. of N.A." International Molders and Foundry Workers Union of North America Pin, 75.
  - "BRAC" Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, 76.
  - "Buy American: Pennsylvania UAW-CAP", 77.
  - "Support UAW", 78.
  - "UAW Community Action Program", 79.
  - "UAW-CIO", September-October, 1948; 80.
  - "For Victory: District 50 U.M.W.A.", 81.
  - "U.M.W. of A. 8 Hours", April 1, 1898; 82.
  - "UMWA Robena, L.U. 6321", 83.
  - "I.U. of M.&S.W. of A.", September 1941; 84.
  - "I.U. of M.&S.W. of A.", October 1941; 85.
  - "W.A.: Workers Alliance of America", 1937; 86.
  - "WA of A: Workers Alliance, Work Security", January-March 1939; 87.
  - "RWDSU, AFL-CIO-CLC" Retail, Wholesale & Department Store Union Button, 88.
  - Keychain Commemorating Address Given by President Johnson at David J. McDonald Hall, U.S.W.A. Dist. 16, April 24, 1964; 89.
  - "A.A. of S.&E.R.E. of A." Amalgamated Association of Street & Electric Railway Employees of America Pin, 90.
  - "Division 65" Amalgamated Association of Street & Electric Railway Employees of America Pin, August 1926; 91.
  - "Gen'l Teamsters, Chauffeurs & Helpers U. 249, A.F. of L.", February 1940; 92.
  - "General Teamsters, Chauffeurs & Helpers 249, A.F. of L.", December 1948; 93.
  - "A.A. of S.E.R.&M.C.E. Greyhound Local Division", March 1939; 94.
  - "Brotherhood of R.S.C. of America", 95.
  - "Transport Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO", 96.
  - "United Transportation Union", 97.
  - "Milk Drivers Union 205, A.F. of L.", October 1948; 98.
  - "Order of Railway Conductors", 99.
  - "Life Member NEA" National Education Association Pin, 100.
  - "Independent Association of Employees, Duquesne Light Co. & Associated Co's", 1942-1943; 101.
  - "A.W.S.E.: Ass'n Westinghouse Salaried Employees", 102.
  - "I'm A Trade Unionist Supporting the Steel Strike", 103.
  - "To Be Sure - I Supported the Westinghouse Strikers", 104.
  - "I Support the National Biscuit Strikers", 105.
  - "Day's Wage $5.00: I.W.W. Defense" Industrial Workers of the World Stamp, 106.
  - "Union Made: International B.&C.W.I.U. of A." Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America Keystone Emblem, 107.
  - "District NFSM Member" National Fraternity of Student Musicians Pin, 1947; 108.
  - "LPIU 50 Years of Service" Lithographers and Photoengravers International Union Pin, 109.
  - "U.R.C.L.&P.W. of A." United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum & Plastic Workers of America Pin, 110.
  - "R.I.A.C.", 111.
  - "A.F.G.E., AFL-CIO" American Federation of Government Employees Pin, 112.
  - "GAU: Graphic Arts International Union", 113.
  - "GAU: Graphic Arts International Union, 35", 114.
  - "Bernard Gloekler Co. Pittsburgh, PA: 100% Club", 115.
  - "I Support UE Strikers: $1 a Week", 1969; 1-8. (Box 3, Tray 2)
  - "Back GE Strikers", 1969; 9-19.
  - "UE CIO: United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America" Pin, 20-29.
  - "UE: United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America" Pin with CIO Scratched Out, c.1950; 30.
  - "UE: United Electrical Radio & Machine Workers of America" Button, 31-33.
  - "St. Gregory's Orthodox Church - Homestead, PA: Founded 1914 - Rebuilt 1950", 34.
  - "50th Golden Jubilee: United Mine Workers of America, John L. Lewis, President", 1940; 35.
  - "United Mine Workers of America Working Button" with an Etched "2", 1933; 36.
  - "B.R.C. of A. Steel City 795", Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, November 1918; 37.
  - "I Support UE Strikers in GE", 1969; 38-45.
  - "Aluminum Workers of America Local 2 C.I.O., May", 46.
  - "Aluminum Workers of America C.I.O.", May 1938; 47.
  - "Labor Day: Johnstown, PA", 1914; 48.
  - "Steel Workers Organizing Committee, C.I.O.: Dues Paid", May 1937; 49.
  - "Boost Our Lyceum Course", 50.
  - "Federation of Telephone Workers, Pennsylvania", 1952; 51.
  - "Union Clerk: R.C.I.P.A." Retail Clerks International Protective Association Button, May 1904; 52.
  - "Denver, PA Local 161: Union Made Cigars", 53.
  - "Central Labor Union Affiliated with AF of L, Meadville, PA", 54.
  - "Gas & By Products Coke Workers, U.M.W. of A.: District 50, Everett Local 12001", 1941; 55.
  - "H.R.E.I.A. Registered" Hotel & Restaurant Employees' International Alliance Pin, 56.